so it looks like i'm moving out earlier
than i anticipated
initially i was expecting not have to do
this until late may or early june but
things changed
it's an interesting reminder that you
can plan and anticipate and prepare for
the future and still not be able to
predict what will happen
plans change and sometimes an
opportunity will arise
even if you don't feel 100 ready for it
it can be hard to know the right course
of action in the moment
but i find that with time and some
courage answers eventually come
it's up to us to listen and understand
ourselves
[Music]
while it will take me at least a month
or so to transition to a new location
i've started the process
by next week i should have all my things
moved out
if you're going through a change right
now be that a physical location or a
more personal transformation
know that you are not alone and change
even if it is hard
can lead to such beautiful things
[Music]
do
it really hasn't hit home yet that i am
leaving i think it will take another
week or so to really start feeling those
emotions
i haven't yet started going through my
more personal items
objects filled with memories and letters
from people i once knew
but i know that it will be a very
cathartic and interesting experience to
go through things that you've kept
hidden away and examine them once again
reevaluating what things mean to you
maybe this video can inspire you to also
welcome the spring and a beautiful new
season by going through what you own and
considering what you value what you
should keep in your life
and maybe what you should let go
[Music]
so
i filled this up without even thinking
about the fact that it would be too
heavy to move
so
um
yeah so i guess um plan b
i
clearly don't know what i'm doing
you think after moving like 17 times in
my life um
i'd know how to pack everything up
really well but i don't i don't
oh my
here we go again
[Music]
do
so i was going through some of my old
things and i found this box and i'm
pretty sure i made this box when i was a
teenager and it is spray painted and it
says
uh neverland on it it is the entire map
of neverland i'm sure it's very
geographically accurate
and
it has some quotes on the side it even
has glitter and tinkerbell on it and yes
i just thought it was too funny and of
course
inside what is there but some
dead leaves
dead flowers
random pieces
of journal paper a picture of a fairy
um
pine cones
some covered with glitter
and
acorn cups and i remember getting these
acorn cups because i remember thinking
they look like little teeny tiny cups
for fairies
and that um it was obviously something i
needed in my life so
i'm questioning my past decisions now i
don't know what i'll do with all these
little things but yeah it's funny to go
through it and look into the past and
just remember
little things about you
[Music]
what's wrong buddy
what do you want
what do you want yeah
chaos
so
um
everything feels so chaotic right now i
have books
everywhere
so i'm definitely still in the process
of kind of getting all that organized
but um yeah it's been a interesting week
it's
it's been a lot of
emotions
yes by the time you have seen this
i will
hopefully be completely moved out it is
interesting to me because for many years
in my life when i was not as healthy
physically and mentally i definitely
felt that any decision that made me
uncomfortable or self-conscious in any
way
was a decision i should avoid making or
i should just always stick to what's in
my comfort zone and what makes me feel
the best and what doesn't challenge me
and i think that's a time of life that
we all find ourselves in in some shape
or form
this move is the very first decision
that i have made that has not been out
of necessity it has been 100
my own decision
and my own wish
to
start a new life and to start a new
phase of life
in a new home
it has been such a wonderful experience
to move everything out it's been very
cathartic i have
found a lot of items from my past
especially
some letters from years ago and certain
mementos that
i
was able to
remember those memories
um
really see them in new light
and understand that it was time to put
those
items aside and put them away and
most of the letters are made of paper so
i did end up composting a lot of those
items and finding natural ways to
dispose of them so there have been
certain experiences i've had in my life
in which i have
forgotten what happened during certain
portions of time i can't recall them
there's kind of a blank space in my
brain
that doesn't allow me to access certain
memories and
it's been interesting through the
process of going through a lot of these
items having some of those memories
return
and it's been very very interesting and
very cathartic
and
yeah it's
it's been good and also bittersweet and
it's uh it's always fascinating what a
fascinating experience to move your
things perhaps this can be inspiration
to all of you to
consider the springtime as a new
beginning we are almost in spring we are
so close and i think it always can be a
good experience to go through the things
you own
and
remember their meaning see if their
meaning has changed maybe
some of these things that you thought
were very very important to you
you feel differently about now i'm
sending so much love and i will see you
very very soon goodbye
[Music]
you